<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:37:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 301120<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sun Jun 30 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Beryl, located several hundred miles east of the Windward Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Southwestern Gulf of Mexico (AL94): <br/>
An area of low pressure located over the southern portion <br/>
of the Bay of Campeche is producing disorganized showers and <br/>
thunderstorms.  Environmental conditions appear conducive for <br/>
further development, and a short-lived tropical depression could <br/>
form before the system moves inland over Mexico on Monday morning.  <br/>
Interests along the Gulf Coast of Mexico should monitor the <br/>
progress of this system.  Regardless of development, heavy rainfall <br/>
associated with the area of low pressure will continue to affect <br/>
portions of Central America and Mexico through early next week.  An <br/>
Air Force reconnaissance aircraft is scheduled to investigate the <br/>
system later today.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL96):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms continue in association with an area of <br/>
low pressure located several hundred miles southwest of the Cabo <br/>
Verde Islands.  Environmental conditions appear conducive for <br/>
additional development of this system, and a tropical depression is <br/>
likely to form by the middle part of this week while it moves <br/>
generally westward at 15 to 20 mph across the eastern and central <br/>
tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:20:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202406301120</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202406301537</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:37:01 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FIND BERYL NOW AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS  CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...LIFE-THREATENING WINDS AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED IN THE WINDWARD  ISLANDS BEGINNING EARLY MONDAY MORNING...
 As of 11:35 AM AST Sun Jun 30
 the center of Beryl was located near 10.8, -54.9
 with movement W at 21 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 962 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>10.8, -54.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:35 AM AST Sun Jun 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>962 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FIND BERYL NOW AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS  CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...LIFE-THREATENING WINDS AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED IN THE WINDWARD  ISLANDS BEGINNING EARLY MONDAY MORNING...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 301445
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Beryl Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1100 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024
 
...VERY DANGEROUS MAJOR HURRICANE BERYL STILL STRENGTHENING AS IT
APPROACHES THE WINDWARD ISLANDS...
...LIFE-THREATENING WINDS AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED THERE BEGINNING
EARLY MONDAY MORNING...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...10.7N 54.9W
ABOUT 355 MI...570 KM ESE OF BARBADOS
ABOUT 470 MI...755 KM E OF GRENADA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...964 MB...28.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Trinidad has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for 
Trinidad.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Barbados
* St. Lucia
* St. Vincent and the Grenadine Islands
* Grenada
* Tobago
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Martinique
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Dominica
* Trinidad
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Lesser Antilles, Hispaniola, Jamaica, 
the Cayman Islands and the remainder of the northwestern Caribbean 
should closely monitor the progress of Beryl.  Additional watches 
or warnings may be required later today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Beryl was located
near latitude 10.7 North, longitude 54.9 West. Beryl is moving
toward the west near 21 mph (33 km/h). A continued quick westward
to west-northwestward motion is expected during the next few days.
On the forecast track, the center of Beryl is expected to move
across the Windward Islands Monday morning and across the
southeastern and central Caribbean Sea late Monday through 
Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 120 mph (195 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Beryl is a category 3 hurricane on 
the Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some additional 
strengthening is forecast through tonight, and Beryl is expected to 
become an extremely dangerous category 4 hurricane before it reaches 
the Windward Islands. 
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles
(185 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from the NOAA and Air 
Force Hurricane Hunters is 964 mb (28.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning
area beginning early Monday morning.  Potentially catastrophic wind 
damage is expected where the eyewall of Beryl moves through portions 
of the Windward Islands, with the highest risk of the core in St. 
Vincent and the Grenadines, and Grenada. 

Wind speeds atop and on the windward sides of hills and mountains 
are often up to 30 percent stronger than the near-surface winds 
indicated in this advisory, and in some elevated locations could be 
even greater.
  
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning
area starting late tonight, making outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch area
starting late tonight.

STORM SURGE:  A life-threatening storm surge will raise water levels
by as much as 6 to 9 feet above normal tide levels in areas of
onshore flow near where the eye makes landfall in the hurricane
warning area.  Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Hurricane Beryl is expected to produce rainfall totals of 
3 to 6 inches across Barbados and the Windward Islands through 
Monday. Localized maxima of 10 inches is possible, especially in the 
Grenadines. This rainfall may cause flash flooding in vulnerable 
areas.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding 
associated with Hurricane Beryl, please see the National Weather 
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf 
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Beryl are expected across
Windward and southern Leeward Islands during the next couple of
days.  These swells are expected to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:45:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN JUN 30 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 301444
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
1500 UTC SUN JUN 30 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.7N  54.9W AT 30/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 275 DEGREES AT  18 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  964 MB
EYE DIAMETER  10 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 105 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT.......100NE  80SE  70SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..135NE  90SE  60SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.7N  54.9W AT 30/1500Z
AT 30/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 10.6N  54.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0000Z 11.2N  57.5W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 12.1N  60.9W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 13.3N  64.3W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 14.6N  68.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 15.6N  72.1W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 16.4N  75.9W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 04/1200Z 17.8N  82.8W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/1200Z 19.2N  88.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE  70SE  40SW  70NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 10.7N  54.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 30/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 30/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/301444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/301444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 301445
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Beryl Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1100 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024
 
Data from the Air Force and NOAA Hurricane Hunters this morning
indicate that Beryl continues to rapidly intensify.  Based on the
data collected, the minimum pressure has fallen significantly to
964 mb and the maximum wind speed is now up to 105 kt.  Although
Beryl is still on the small side, the wind field is a little larger
than previously noted with the tropical-storm-force winds estimated 
to extend up to 100 n mi from the center and hurricane-force winds 
up to 25 n mi from the eye.  Satellite images show that Beryl has a 
classic major hurricane pattern with a clear and circular eye and 
symmetric convective pattern surrounding it.
 
Beryl continues to move swiftly westward at 18 kt steered by a 
strong subtropical ridge to its north.  The hurricane has been 
moving a little to the south of most of the model predictions over 
the past day or two.  A continued quick west to west-northwest 
motion is forecast during the next several days as the ridge remains 
the primary steering feature.  This should take the core of Beryl 
across the Windward Islands Monday morning and then across much the 
Caribbean Sea during the following few days.  The NHC track forecast 
has been nudged to the south of the previous prediction and lies 
close to the various consensus aids.
 
The major hurricane has rapidly intensified since it formed a
couple of days ago, and given the continued conducive environmental
conditions and compact inner core, it will likely strengthen some
more through tonight.  Beryl is expected to be a very dangerous
category 4 hurricane when it moves through Windward Islands.  The
models show a gradual increase in shear when the system moves
across the Caribbean Sea and that should cause Beryl's intensity to
level off and then gradually weaken.  However, Beryl is expected to
remain a significant hurricane through the next 5 days.  The
intensity forecast is a little above the previous one and in good
agreement with the HCCA and IVCN models.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Beryl is expected to be an extremely dangerous Category 4 
hurricane when it reaches the Windward Islands. This is a very 
dangerous situation and residents in these areas should listen to 
local government and emergency management officials for any 
preparedness and/or evacuation orders. All preparations should be 
rushed to completion today.
 
2. Potentially catastrophic hurricane-force winds, a 
life-threatening storm surge, and damaging waves are expected 
when Beryl passes over portions of the Windward Islands with the 
highest risk of the core in St. Vincent and the Grenadines, and 
Grenada beginning early Monday morning.  Hurricane Warnings are in 
effect for much of the Windward Islands.

3. Heavy rainfall and localized flooding are expected across the
Windward Islands through Monday.
 
4. Beryl is expected to remain a powerful hurricane as it moves 
across the Caribbean Sea later this week and interests in 
Hispaniola, Jamaica, the Cayman Islands and the remainder of the 
northwestern Caribbean should monitor its progress, There is large 
forecast uncertainty  at days 4 and 5 and users should not focus on 
the specific details of the track or intensity forecast.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/1500Z 10.7N  54.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  01/0000Z 11.2N  57.5W  120 KT 140 MPH
 24H  01/1200Z 12.1N  60.9W  120 KT 140 MPH
 36H  02/0000Z 13.3N  64.3W  115 KT 130 MPH
 48H  02/1200Z 14.6N  68.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 60H  03/0000Z 15.6N  72.1W  110 KT 125 MPH
 72H  03/1200Z 16.4N  75.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
 96H  04/1200Z 17.8N  82.8W   95 KT 110 MPH
120H  05/1200Z 19.2N  88.3W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:45:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN JUN 30 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 301445
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
1500 UTC SUN JUN 30 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
10.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 54.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
105 KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
VERACRUZ MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FRONTERA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)
MERIDA MX      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  27(35)
COZUMEL MX     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)
COZUMEL MX     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  25(29)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
BELIZE CITY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)
PUERTO BARRIOS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
PUERTO BARRIOS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  20(33)
GUANAJA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)
GUANAJA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  11(14)   X(14)   X(14)
PT GALLINAS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
PT GALLINAS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CURACAO        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   4(17)   X(17)   X(17)
CURACAO        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
CURACAO        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  12(21)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   6(19)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   1(11)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  42(43)   6(49)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   4(22)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  29(52)   X(52)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  19(24)   X(24)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   X(12)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  42(42)  21(63)   X(63)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  17(33)   X(33)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  11(17)   X(17)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   1(27)   X(27)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  28(29)   1(30)   X(30)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  43(48)   X(48)   X(48)
CAPE BEATA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)
CAPE BEATA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  12(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
AVES           34  X   2( 2)  20(22)   7(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
AVES           50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   5( 5)   8(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  1   4( 5)   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  2  41(43)  16(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
SAINT LUCIA    50  X   6( 6)   6(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
SAINT LUCIA    64  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  2  74(76)  14(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
SAINT VINCENT  50  X  29(29)  21(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
SAINT VINCENT  64  X   8( 8)  15(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
BARBADOS       34  2  68(70)   1(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
BARBADOS       50  1  15(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
BARBADOS       64  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GRENADA        34  1  76(77)  18(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
GRENADA        50  X  34(34)  42(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)
GRENADA        64  X  14(14)  37(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
 
TRINIDADTOBAGO 34  2  77(79)   2(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
TRINIDADTOBAGO 50  X  39(39)   2(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
TRINIDADTOBAGO 64  X  15(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
PORT OF SPAIN  34  1  15(16)   3(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
PORT OF SPAIN  50  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
JUANGRIEGO     34  X   2( 2)  13(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
JUANGRIEGO     50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/301445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Update Statement</title>
<description>Issued at 1135 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT62 KNHC 301536
TCUAT2
 
Hurricane Beryl Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1135 AM AST Sun Jun 30 2024

...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FIND BERYL NOW AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS 
CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE...
...LIFE-THREATENING WINDS AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED IN THE WINDWARD 
ISLANDS BEGINNING EARLY MONDAY MORNING...
 
NOAA and Air Force Reserve hurricane hunter aircraft data indicate
that Beryl has strengthened to an extremely dangerous category 4 
hurricane. The maximum sustained winds are estimated to be 130 mph 
(215 km/h) with higher gusts.
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1135 AM AST...1535 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...10.8N 54.9W
ABOUT 350 MI...565 KM ESE OF BARBADOS
ABOUT 460 MI...740 KM E OF GRENADA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...962 MB...28.41 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:37:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT2+shtml/301536.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT2+shtml/301536.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/144818.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:48:18 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/144818.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:48:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/144818.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/144818.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
